it sounds ok stream earlier no it's
streaming time now Bros Labor Day open
end not application low er no
applications okay try again open em you
know ok security settings now probably
most of the stream is going to be me
trying to get this to work yeah I don't
know about these audio problems guys
like I hear this sometimes so it
probably isn't all trolls we're getting
a lot we're gonna oh yes on exciting
world Oh perfect
let's go
drag and drop games here we're going to
speedrun Super Mario World dismiss Super
Nintendo oh yes perfect ah yes this is
actually gonna work
controls now I have here a ps4
controller only because I couldn't find
my Xbox controllers so sorry Sony if I'm
hacking the ship I deeply apologize you
can sue me just kidding don't do that
mmm Wow they already have good mappings
for it
yo emulations gotten good yeah let's
play all right I don't actually know how
to speedrun this game but we're gonna
try our best well okay so actually hang
on oh sorry no they're not me back let's
exit full-screen here go to my twitch
ease put my twitch ease over here and
let me see if I can fix sound display
capture video capture device audio
output capture create now device no
device
[Music]
no mic ox
yeah I don't know how to help you guys
with the broken audio but we're here and
we're gonna try our best to speedrun
this game let's go oh I had to do some
cloud shit there with like Yoshi and his
tongue I've seen speedruns before all
right so I know when you speedrun you
just keep pressing right and sometime
you press jump oh I should have just ran
into the thing I think the 14 is
slightly slower all right so I don't
know anything about speedrunning I don't
know like what routes to take or
anything but I think we're gonna go to
star world right how do I do this level
I've seen the speedrunners do it and it
wasn't like this I need peace speed up
thank you sir can you hear me turn the
volume up a little bit okay we should
watch a real speedrunner do this super
mario world speed right now they're just
cheating with credits warp glitch i want
to do that crap this may be
oh here he's on this left okay okay so I
did that too I might want to host
character but like we literally did that
last night
oh he jumps there okay jump on the Koopa
okay let's try that again
[Music]
he's betting's hard guys let's try it
again see I don't have peace you see
when he's sick sounds a little Mario
thing oh so close that time guys all
right we're gonna jump there there and
then up
all right don't worry never fear try it
again in order to be a speed runner
you must keep trying alright good I'm
good at speedrunning this level
I lost speed there I got a time nap
better lag frames oh yeah okay alright
we're good at speedrunning that level
all right now we just got to get good at
this next level wait on big Mario does
that matter I won't be big Mario after I
died
let's try that again jump all right I
gotta land up there I got a jump no no
no no no no no no no no no no watch how
this guy did it in the video look I saw
him do it
jump jump jump
look at that pro scale look at that guy
do it he can do it I can do it jump too
soon
[Music]
oh yeah getting better guys I'm getting
better
[Music]
oh do you guys see that so close yeah
we're trying to speed run brows no that
was so close guys that was so close it's
gonna feel great when we get it look it
from where he jumps okay all right
that's a good point
[Music]
watch in slow motion
he just has skill I got to figure out
again you know what if I can just get
more speed on the first level we can
make it up I'm gonna why he gets that
shout
oh he like does weird shit he does he
goes glitches this is a glitchless speed
on you guys now okay yeah we got to get
my timing better on that oh yeah look at
that that's the route I know the route
now oh yeah we definitely don't want to
get that last charge of Chuck oh yeah
you see how I didn't jump there - I'm
getting better at speedrunning guys
[Music]
you're only gonna try this once boy oh
did you see that did you see that shit
I'm a great speed runner I supposed to
jump on that Cooper app alright
[Music]
oh yeah I'm getting reliable at it guys
I had to jump on that Koopa didn't you
see what he was doing I can't lose my
pee speed no we don't do reverse
engineering if you're looking for that
you're on the wrong Channel we speedrun
Super Mario oh yeah all right fine you
won't go we'll go cupola yeah that was
that was douse dumb that was dumb
[Music]
oh yeah
speedrun bros what are we doing this
level P speed spin jumps all right cool
oh that was was that a shell jump that
looked hard okay we've got to do a lot
of spin jumps now if you want to learn
to hack oh wait how I hold I'll hold
them with the Run button n spin jump
speed run okay we beat that level very
fast
[Music]
I'll find somebody's I fail is purple
said back too many spins oh no we only
do things that don't teach anybody
anywhere like how to poorly speedrun
mario what does he do about that guy
that guy seems like the enemy
Chay's in oh did you see that low-speed
spin jump oh that was sick though let's
try again you know what they say in
Galaxy Quest never give up never
surrender let's go alright then spin
jumps are faster oh that was bad I lost
so much time on that my splits hey
you're watching my stream we streamed
Super Mario speed running very poorly
you want to get good at something you
got to practice very hard like to see
this jump when I started speedrunning I
couldn't get this jump but now I get it
most of the time yeah speed one skill
don't even think I had to jump down
going low koopa piece beat did that on
purpose guys
I don't think I have to jump here I
think I do this Ronnie Cheryl went
backwards you never do that in a
speedrun if you're pressing the left
arrow in a speedrun you're speedrunning
wrong all right this is the level we
just run and spin jump a lot we have to
throw the shell up here up yeah I get
that fish I spin Jobert can I show my
controller on screen not supported I
[Music]
want to show my controller inputs on
screen for the pleasure of all of you
watching at home a gamepad viewer
no display mo I don't know about this
[Music]
oh come on let's see what he did about
that fish has more of a dry humor me not
a nut I mean that's in your face does he
do that with the shell he does it so
fast
[Music]
that's some cargo cult speedrunning
right there I I got the shell cuz he got
the show those mines it's tricking you
guys mushroom with so many lag frames
just levels hard okay run spin jump down
spin jump they're at a second platform
how do you really learn to do this
[Music]
second part see he never goes in the
water
it keeps p-speed all level only have one
life left tweeze hats and get infinite
lives no now we only use hacks on this
channel this is the Tom Cruise channel
there's no hack it we speedrun mario
okay we're gonna go for the low spin
jump around the guy always smash that
fun mash that button yeah ah we hit them
[Music]
guys but you know what they say in
speedrunning you gotta keep trying you
get faster with every run purpose
watching to do some purpose I don't want
to be big Mary ow
[Music]
yeah you see there we did we did noise
cancel no I don't know why I didn't make
the noise when I lost my thing hey hey
hey slow run hey I want to see you do
better
let's see your speedrun skills brah
alright this jumps hard I got to focus
guys I really got to focus on this
[Laughter]
you're gonna make fun of my speedrun oh
yeah look at that look at that I get
that
reliably now don't low Koopa nope I
landed the other specified purpose okay
so I know about speedrunning you never
press the left button the only choice
you have is how hard you want to press
the right binder see these are the
buttons don't press this one is this
isn't speedrun and you only press that
one alright guys
oh no I have to do this one again this
one this one's hard
[Music]
ken did that right how to do that shell
track oh come on I hit it with the spin
jump let's watch his route really
careful
okay early spin jump there there there I
don't know what that shell shit is the
early spin jump stuff early spin jump
down their second platform go go
no I think he does I don't know what he
does that he just lands on both
something like that with the shell hey
tech fish okay let's watch carefully
one spin to there spin to there
spin to there but you get no okay only
first platform there okay let's try that
I don't really spend jobs here second
platform go go first platform perfect do
the weird shell trick up fish killed me
how does he do that
terr second platform first platform pick
the shell up turn drop it jump should we
Google have a shit I don't know I'm
trying to figure it out okay early spin
jump go second platform huh messed up
messed up and now I did that I'm so bad
I'm the worst speed runner ever guys I
have no future and this I should just
give up and win self-driving cars
okay let's watch castle
low-spin job I don't know how the guy
did that I knew did you go tutor me
what are you doing area 51 you want to
teach me how to speedrun area oh yeah
got it
I got it no I didn't mean to pick that
up no but at least I can get first jump
[Music]
all right guys you know what they say in
speedrunning do it again let me find a
Super Mario World all exits where they
don't do Glen Chao kill them jump spin
jump over that
you just did that for nothing man yeah
that looks very similar to my speedrun
[Music]
we could try game genie I don't know is
that how these people practice I met you
jump to there no no no okay let's do
that again
this one cat one jump there jump there
spin jump over that jump there see
oh my we're gonna do that spin job I
gotta keep my oh yeah kill it with them
speed guys I really got to focus on this
part got it no okay let's watch him a
little more carefully because I saw what
he did for the first thing well it
seemed he has a there there there keep
running there there kay jump on them
both go jump over hit that alright I see
[Music]
I don't like I should learn game
mechanics probably just what do you
think you get something no oh okay okay
I see what I have to do
did you see how that one was different I
just got scared guys you know what they
say in speedrunning though you can't
give up you got to keep just going you
did a second jump there and then their
lamb there nice spin jump I'll go do the
spin jump transition better good up
differential
Oh guys please donate to my channel I'm
sorry if you'd rather like I'd be doing
something else productive with my life
like programming or hacking but this is
a marriage of speed running channel we
speedrun mario very poorly see that's
how poorly we speedrun mario I see what
I have to do Mac oh look at that that
was good that was legit fine we'll go
low Koopa I don't have P speed that was
good ball lasted just gotta keep going
I'm not pressing the go right harder
[Music]
where is he when he jumps that's a good
idea I might want to host character like
we literally did that last night
frame perfect trick yeah do that again
[Music]
we almost got to go hi Cooper that time
with one life I always spend jump
yeah second platform to make it all the
way to the other platform there over
[Music]
engines I'm pretty good at this level of
guys
[Music]
oh it says she'll jump question mark so
maybe that's not that hard maybe that
actually is a really hard Trek mean
Chardon Chuck well this is the best
speed I've ever had guys hi Koopa what
does he do there he jumps jumps over all
that I got high coop of that time and
I'm pretty happy I'm just making up
speed running lights okay early spin
second plat first plat she'll jump oh
did you see that was close
oh that was the speed run if I've ever
seen one guys that was fast
I had great time without me let me put
my splits in how do I get one of those
split counter things
I'll get one soon
[Music]
low jump spin okay I've got to figure
out what to do about that guy okay spin
spin oh he just managed to spin below
him he's good oh my get down everything
kills you in castles how do I get off
the wall
[Music]
oh I'm a speed runner i hate auto
scrollers caution about that
[Music]
No okay fine
I gotta figure out a better kill these
bosses how does he do it bro he's just
going down the wall Wallace caller
[Music]
yeah you see that this is speedrunning
scale bras yeah mash buttons fast
buttons math buttons alright what I do
now I gotta I gotta learn Kate mechanics
she gets special exit here we gave you
the special exit see where did you get
the Cape on the first guy let's go donut
land guys so he did that way faster all
right what are Cape mechanics you can
fly forever with this Cape I just don't
have to do it let's look out Mary Oh
world Cape mechanics follow-up not
useless yeah okay just stay in the air
alternately pushing left and right on
the died but I'm getting it kind of yeah
I don't want to talk about we used to
continue in my speedrun
[Music]
what what Kate back not on mushroom no I
didn't want to continue
no how do I get continued fine you take
you have to come back here Cape come
back here Cape it's terrible oh I'm
terrible go back to the beginning this
guy with tape tape there's got a cape
come here Cape there my cape who's a
cape guy gonna continue
[Music]
okay bro getting better no right here
and donut Plains one is a great place to
learn Katy go back to the other one
Mario grab the loop is down check is a
face hey see that Cape cancel guys
[Music]
now okay that took way too long where do
I go next
look at him he just Brants over the
whole thing does she is pro he got
instant fast fly of course like sugar
should have gotten that one I gotta go
for this secret here no no oh this is
keep shell I know keep shout
[Music]
okay fine where's he gets shell well he
goes in that pipe this is their throwing
pipe okay we need to get wings keep the
shell I've seen this guy no I don't want
that I want the shell
oh my god really
oh there goes my shell scenario swims
faster when he has an object
[Music]
okay fine
do I need Cape for this level
I need Cape for this level no that's the
wow that was boss look at him he's boss
with that Xiao well I don't know about
all that
let's see what exit I have to take why
up there with the pay okay
[Music]
with my pika
is my pink
[Music]
big boo can't hurt you actually little
boobs I probably shouldn't have lost
cape
rainy cape for next level I do
[Music]
spin jump cancel perfect there's a
mushroom oh no I can't cancel bro you
are a king I want cake how does he do
that thing Reid cancels their workouts
like that how to play the next level a
water level get the Yoshi don't feed the
Yoshi
take the Yoshi and swim over everything
until you get to that fishes and then
swim under everything down earlier oops
[Music]
hi ocean
can what I do in the next level fly up
with the p ms no now I have to go back
get flying know what a better idea if I
get blue Yoshi can't believe she eat
anything apply this is an alternative
route you guys fly eat fucking cloud man
now my blue Yoshi okay put feathers in
the box okay fine
new Tom Cruise's here - shit talk my
Mario's speed someone get Kanye on the
phone this has to end
how's Kanye gonna help can Kanye speed
run
oh no that was terrible I was looking at
you guys
Oh guys I don't know the last time I
saved if I die okay you gotta focus okay
let's get double cape is that what you
want the whole camp no if I kill them
like that I don't get any cape
[Music]
you only get one King don't mess it off
no I did that last time secure shit eat
that Yoshi you're like oh my god how do
you come back no that was bullshit wait
how's this supposed to work the NTIA
like jump off no shoes mechanics at this
level because I haven't beat it
oh thanks for the cloud bro I just stole
his cloud thanks bro
[Music]
this is an alternative strap it's called
cloud steel I did the cloud steel strap
I don't see what I'm doing the next
level I fly over the whole thing with my
wings that I don't have fast all right
all right come on please
okay let's get gameshark wings gameshark
wings superman i get wings settings
select cheat start his cape mary oh oh
they know what's up
wait where's my cape just like she start
his cape mario i don't understand
[Music]
I'm not Cape Marriott well limited lives
let's just start these aren't good
cheats
unlimited alive that's a good cheap
limited lives I don't really know if
this works Cape start as Cape Mario
start us fired
[Music]
Oh unlimited lives works but not
starting is Kate Mary yeah let's just
die I have an idea we gotta practice we
didn't speed one of the Star Wars enough
anyway I don't navel on the bias I'm
done with cheating guys
cheating's wrong don't cheat we're gonna
get double cape over here come on Kate
[Music]
okay remember the strats guys spin jump
figure out somehow how to do that Cape
cancel down
[Music]
I'm trying to clamp I don't know how we
get that I fine
twit cheese I'm sorry did I call you
slack ease I'm sorry
scobie's I'm sorry I know your pitches
at oh I know this strat oh this is the
easiest I love the straps oh no I said
yo I know my fucking cake that was
literally the worst thing that could
have happened in this level now I'm
gonna have to play it that was literally
the worst thing that could have happened
in this level guys yo she ate the star
[Music]
you see five swimming fishies you want
to go down yeah oh my god this level
takes so long now those fish died try to
follow me guys cheating's for losers we
don't cheat
[Music]
where's my tape was my cake add cheap
good tape
[Music]
powerup selection it's this dad cheats
ox and sheep power off press often
select eyebrow jacking your cloud drop
[Music]
never mind
press come these don't oh I have to turn
it off there's only in the levels wait I
had a cake
how'd I get that did you see my cape
oh I figured how to do it okay oh yeah k
bro
[Music]
I'm trying to be pro gamer guys okay
let's say you play this level was it to
me as well okay I did that you run fast
fly immediately please wise under the
level that looks hard I might have to go
back to donut secret and practice my
cape perfect
fast fly immediately please
[Music]
how did he do that oh yeah you see that
skill tiger P speed again so anywhere in
this level I can get P speed now flux
I'm waking up at eight and a half hours
thanks for telling me
but see here's the problem we have to go
down there unless we can floppy let's
just enable infinite lives
[Music]
okay you really have to get the timing
on that right not like that
I know I got a work on the Cape mechanic
guys I'm getting better don't worry have
you been here if you've been with me
since Yoshi's Island three you see how
fast I improve it Thanks oops
[Music]
deaf Lila I did this twice
he flies on direct right path I
immediately please why do I want this
Yoshi yeah okay you're right just fly
around at the timing haven't just freak
out on him down low I don't want this
Yoshi you know Leo she's too long
[Music]
see I'm going just too low this is not
that easy - we try to do ML speedruns
after this we'll try to learn to
speedrun like learning to speedrun from
watching youtube videos I'm gonna be
pretty cool actually if I could really
do that that would be like a super paper
worthy thing no see okay it's very hard
to actually gain altitude while doing
that it's doable but yeah I know I know
it's timing I know but there's no way to
like fly around should I go to a
different level no no no no I could
never do this in fact when I saw this in
speedruns I didn't know that that was
possible with the Cape I didn't know
that it was possible to stay airborne
forever so not every six-year-old could
do it I sure as hell couldn't do it when
I was sex see I was so close there I
have to work on gaining altitude once I
lose
[Music]
close close close close and get me guys
I'm got it don't worry don't worry I
won't keep you to it she's here forever
yeah it's written in assembly like a lot
of people would disassemble yeah I'm
trying to fly the entire board I know
that's what the guy did in the video
[Music]
game class okay okay you know just so I
can do the flying mechanic I mean I
understand it it's just time but
practicing there is just as just as good
as practicing anywhere else
the trick is will not play flesh welcome
to my channel but we're trying to
speedrun Super Mario World
[Music]
ah so close I'm getting it back well you
don't even have to press forward can
actually just press back it seems oh
[Music]
this is so easy you just press back oh
this is the easiest thing in the world
okay food ate so much food today we ate
food drank beers Labor Day oh this is
the simplest mechanic once you figure it
out homes you know what the problem was
I told myself you never press the back
button and speed Ronnie all right how to
play this level oh why don't I just go
there all right
Bowser skip over 1 2 now go into 2
all right we're not gonna try that well
actually maybe we can oh no you got to
keep your piece beat in the door I've
seen this before
well dive and you want to okay I say
room seven takes you I don't even know
about that do any music he doesn't jump
and then up yeah okay does that and then
he goes to the door then Bram suck I say
[Music]
my name is the door
I love the new Eminem album I think it's
great I said it was fire fine oh my god
this is so slow I thought this was
speedrun bro I'm seven please
how's he keep that
[Music]
what what what dish you thought was wack
see how he does that he jumps first
frame jump and then he still has it okay
no damage boost
which it was the desk she gun kills all
right you can dis little Zen and little
yachty only wise people suck I'm seven
please
[Music]
this one's hard
alright let's just beat this level by
Bowser going down old-school style with
Mario skill and cheats
[Music]
Cape cancel the last guy what is this
he's memorized this why people are dumb
that's a great question
I think it's led
[Music]
this guy
[Laughter]
[Music]
that's fly
all right thousand gonna die
[Music]
the Bowser I need some Mecca Cooper's to
throw out you throw Mecca Cooper's know
and what's too far off the screen for me
to get uses a complete ambassadors
traveling in do because it does yoshi
coin shit
and princess give me a mushroom love
mushrooms oh yeah I needed that clean
been flying around like a moron
my pals like give me something to throw
at you come on a marble no no I want
marble skip no no marble whoops my
princess is in another castle after I
fought this asshole in a smiley balloon
mecha Koopas thank you I missed oh you
gonna drop another marble
I ain't marbles marbles marbles eat you
too maca Kubas thank you die Bowser
hey princess can I have a mushroom
princess all of you give me mushrooms
and then you're stuck in the smiling
pool with the weird guy oh god no
no the mushroom where'd it go
what's the sake of Bowser's shit Macca
Koopa yeah mega Koopa wait what no that
wouldn't kill them that want to kill
them do I have to replay this level Oh
No
okay it was literally one mecha kupo
away from killing him I don't know how
to do that part with wing yeah I was
living my god
[Music]
hate that guy down all right let's just
keep this guy I know I said that last
time I was trying
hate those things
hate that thing hate that one we tried
to Cape cancel Mecca Cooper couldn't
come to door with me
Oh yo if you guys donate ten bucks I'll
do programming yeah
see that Cape cancel don't get lucky
twice you know
mega Koopas thank you
[Music]
did you donate $10 will do programming
no one donated any dollars for my love
quality Mario no Machine Gun Kelly just
Eminem back I'll watch that no no no
whatever you can't pay me to do reverse
engineering but you can't pay me for
programming we will do 30 minutes of
programming after this if you donate $10
we'll go back to Gantz you can do Ganz
but you gotta donate $10 donate $10
that guy's hard look at that one it's
hard he's hard to see look I can't get
around him
[Music]
if you don't need $5 that's not enough
and you tank
how about you donate seven and then
someone else will donate three because
we don't get money by the time I beat
Mario I'm going to sleep or we could
have a long night of program but I need
money
[Music]
guys no I'm not even like trying to
speed run anymore I'm just trying to
play Mario
[Music]
okay point one Bitcoin hell yeah bro if
you don't make point one Bitcoin I'm
sold
point one now I jumped over no he came
back frustrating as hell that was so
hard
even with Cape Qi and on limited lives
this is really sad
focus focus for this episode is play
good mag don't play fast Mario play good
man you know we're here to speedrun if
you promised we'd speedrun but $10 so
who wants to donate $10 then we'll do
program Pico coin was your all coin shit
don't know Pico coins yeah we can do
that we can do whatever whoever donate
to be $10 wants yeah that's it I just
jumped over yeah that's right that's
right don't even hate these guys
[Music]
I was spinning so good I don't even know
what happened
[Music]
by Bowser let's go
yeah I'm getting better cheating no we
won't do reverse engineering but we will
do whatever programming you want if you
pay me $10 sorry I talked to shill and
play Mario at the same time I love money
[Music]
No yeah we can do no js' or rust we can
do whatever you want viewers choice
you gotta donate ten dollars
I know nodejs under us yeah I know them
both what do you want me to code let me
know what you want me to co it was
called it hate these fire-breathing
assholes what do you want me to make
emulator for as NES I don't think I can
do that that fast
[Music]
wait what I'm laying on his head hitbox
no hacking I'm just gonna fly away I
don't want to fight Bowser anymore oh
yeah of course that's why I landed of
course some big barrier now - I didn't
expect that
[Music]
to mushroom not beatable now never you
guys donated I beat the game I mean
money this game wasn't free you know it
cost me $50 and if you're saying if
you're saying that you saw me at the
beginning of the stream I just lost a
thing if you if you say you saw me at
the beginning of the stream download
this for free off the internet well that
would be true but
marbles oh you got a common compatible
car congratulations welcome that was a
scam I even get that other Mecca Koopa
they do all this like shit to skip the
Bowser fight and speed runs and the
Wonder I can't do this look the guy
cheats uses glitches with all Bowser
fights just a few did good
like Bowser fights no
right
yeah take that Bowser no no no no no
there's glitchless speed rocks
I'm going to rescue the princess if it's
the last thing I do
tonight unless you donate $10 and then
to program washing
Macca Koopa thank you cheating
dear boy I'll go back to twitch s for 10
bucks I'm a cheap programmer come will
this used to be a programming stream hey
hey hey hey Marilyn princess of a
platonic relationship thank you for
subscribing to my channel they're gonna
take a vacation this is nothing there's
nothing untoward about that
please donate to my stream yeah first
time you guys alright so now I want you
to edit that stream together and then
we're gonna post a fake speedrun cuz
we're gonna be just like Billy Mitchell
you guys know Billy Mitchell will be
just like Billy Mitchell he's a famous
video game player who cheated
yes sissy this was work for Mario but
this was in captivity though really if
you were caught up by like that guy
alright next time we'll have splits and
we'll try to get better
wait did you really sub to my channel
did you really just sup to my channel
when you stop normally I clap when
people sup know you've been stalked for
as long as I can remember don't try that
shit you resolved I don't know about
that I do appreciate your subscription
but well I always clap Joker
[Music]
no I'll never be like Billy Mitchell
don't be like Billy Mitchell guys if you
give me $10 I'm giving you no nevermind
it's too late I'm going to sleep see you
guys bye twitchy's thanks for not giving
me $10 and now I don't hit me anything
during my super heart's chief speaking